A Guide to the Papers of Robert Frost, 1873-1981
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
- Series II. Letters
  - Subseries A. Correspondence of Robert Frost, Elinor Frost and the Frost Family
    - Subseries 2. Robert Frost, Elinor Frost and the Frost Family
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett(incomplete), [1918 Summer]; ALS, 6 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1919 April 7; ALS, 8 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett(incomplete), 1920 October 16; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1921 December 20]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [ca. 1922 June]; ALS, 10 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [ca. 1922 August]; ALS, 6 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1925 December 11; ALS, 3 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1926 January]; ALS, 3 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1926 May 26]; ALS, 8 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1926 December 23; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - John T. Bartlett to Gorham Munson, 1927 April 30; TLS, 7 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1927 November 1; ALS, 6 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1928 June]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1928 winter]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1931 March 17; Telegram (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1931 May 7]; ALS, 6 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1931 September 8]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1933 December 5; ALS, 7 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T.and Margaret Bartlett. Christmas Card: "The Lone Striker." Inscribed "J. T. B.'s from R. F. 1933", 1933 December; ANS (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost and Elinor Frost to John T.and Margaret Bartlett. Christmas Card: Two Tramps in Mud-Time." Inscribed by Frost "To John and Margaret [ ] most often thought of as they used to be in Derry", 1934 December; AN (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, [1935 January 1]; ALS, 8 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to 1910 Class Reunion. [transcript copy], 1935 August; Telegram (Box 6)
      - Robert S. Newdick to John T. Bartlett, 1935 December 9; TLS, 2 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert S. Newdick to John T. Bartlett, 1936 October 11; TLS, 1 p. (Box 6)
      - J[ohn] T. B[artlett]to Robert S. Newdick, 1936 November 19; TL (carbon), 1 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost and Elinor Frost to John T. Bartlett and Margaret Bartlett. Christmas Card: "To a Young Wretch", 1937 December; Card (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1943 January 20; ALS, 2 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T. Bartlett, 1945 June 15; ALS, 3 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to John T.and Margaret Bartlett. Christmas Card: "A Young Birch", 1946 December; Card (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Margaret Bartlett, 1947 December 26; ALS, 2 p. (Box 6)
      - Alan Swallow to Margaret Bartlett, 1949 April 7; TLS (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Margaret Bartlett, [1949 November 22]; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Padraic [Colum], 1928 September 18; ALS, 3 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Mr. Van Loon, ca. 1918-1920; ALS, 3 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [John Hall] Wheelock, 1937 November 21; ALS, 1 p. (Box 6)
      - Bruce Rogers to Emily E. Connor of the Marchbanks Press, 1950 May 18; ALS (Box 6)
        Concerning Rogers's design for The Complete Poems of Robert Frost for the Limited Editions Club.
      - Bruce Rogers to Emily E. Connor of the Marchbanks Press, 1950 May 20; ALS (Box 6)
      - Bruce Rogers to Emily E. Connor of the Marchbanks Press, 1950 May 25; ALS (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Ernest C. Jewell, promise to pay, 1902 May 24; ANS, 1 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Elinor Frost to Grace Hazard Conkling, [1921] January 22; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Grace Hazard Conkling, 1921 June 28; ALS, 7 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Grace Hazard Conkling, 1921 December 29; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Elinor Frost to Grace Hazard Conkling, [1924] November 4; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [Clifton] Waller Barrett, 1957 January 24; TLS, 1 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - K[athleen Morrison]to Clifton Waller Barrett, [1963 May 29]; ANS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
        Enclosing copies of two autograph poems, beginning "There was never naught" and "Behind his back as he went off to work."
      - William A. Jackson to Robert Frost, 1957 January 15; TLS, 1 p. (Box 6)
      - Elinor Frost to Leona Harvey, [ca. 1920 June]; ALS, 6 p. (Box 6)
      - Lesley Frost to Hilda and Vera Harvey, 1938 April 18; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Vera Harvey, [1941 January 5]; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Hilda and Vera Harvey, 1941 December 22; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Vera Harvey, 1942 September 24; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Vera Harvey, 1945 June 3; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Vera Harvey, 1946 September 15; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Vera Harvey, 1951 December; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Elinor Frost to Vera Harvey, n.y. February 2; ALS, 6 p. (Box 6)
      - Elinor Frost to Vera Harvey, n.y. August 14; ALS, 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Wrapper addressed to "Misses Hilda and Vera Harvey" by Robert Frost, ANS (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Edith H. Blaney, 1916 October 15; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - [ Clifton Waller Barrett] to K[athleen] Morrison, 1962 September 27; TL (carbon), 1 p. (Box 6)
      - K[athleen Morrison]to [Clifton] Waller [Barrett], 1962 October 19; TLS, 1 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, [1937 June 8]; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, [1937] September 20; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, 1937 October 11; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, [1937 November 26]; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, written on typed poem by unknown author, [1937 November]; ALS, 3 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, 1937 December 14; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, [1937 December 26]; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert S. Newdick to Robert Frost, 1938 January 3; TL (carbon), 1 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, 1938 January 18; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, 1938 June 2; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, 1938 June 2; ALS, 1 p. w/two envs (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, [1938 July 20]; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, with mimeographed blurb on Frost from Standard American Encyclopedia, 1938 August 14; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, 1938 September 17; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, 1938 December 2; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Robert S. Newdick, 1939 February 12; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Otto Manthey-Zorn to Robert Frost, [1952]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [William] Prescott [Frost], [ca. 1931]; ALS, 3 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [William] Prescott Frost, 1933 May 11; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to William Prescott Frost, 1933 December 21; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [William] Prescott [Frost], 1934 [February 22]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [William] Prescott Frost, [1934 February 23]; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [William] Prescott Frost, 1935 August 22; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [William] Prescott Frost, 1938 April 8; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [William] Prescott Frost, [1939 November 1]; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [William] Prescott Frost, 1940 October 12; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [William] Prescott Frost, [1940] December 10; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to William Prescott Frost, [1941 September 29]; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [William] Prescott Frost, 1943 February 1; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to William Prescott Frost, 1946 January 16; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [William] Prescott Frost, [1947 September 13]; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to [William] Prescott [Frost], 1962 August 17; TLS, 1 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Mr. Grover, 1935 December; ALS, 1 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to J. J. [Lankes], 1936 February 6; ALS (copy), 4 p. (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to Lawrance R. Thompson, [1936 March 26]; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 6)
      - Robert Frost to "Dear Kids", [1915 February]; ALS, 1 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Carol Frost, [1915]; APC (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1917 September 26; ALS, 2 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1917 November 11]; ALS, 8 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1917 November 13; ALS, 8 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1917 December 3; ALS, 2 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1917 December 9; ALS, 5 p. (Box 7)
        Enclosing printed poems, "Portion" by Leslie Jennings and "I Stood at Twilight" by Bernice Van Slyke, with autograph comments on each.
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1917] Mon morning; ALS, 2 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1917] Mon afternoon; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, with ANS from Robert Frost on last page, [1917] Tues noon; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1917] Thurs morning; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1917] Thur afternoon; ALS, 6 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1917] Fri evening; ALS, 8 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1917]; ALS, 6 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1917]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1918 March 18; ALS, 2 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1918 May 13; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, with ANS from Robert Frost on top of first page, [1918 June]; ALS, 6 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918 September 23]; ALS, 5 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918 October 5]; ALS, 8 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918 October 7]; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918 October 10]; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1918 October 18; ALS, 7 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918 October 21]; ALS, 3 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1918 October 24; ALS, 9 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, writing two AMsS, "The Aim Was Song" and "The Cow's in the Corn" following the text, 1918 November 5; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918 Fall]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918] Mon morning; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918] Mon morning; ALS, 3 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley and Irma Frost, [1918] Mon morning; ALS, 3 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley and Irma Frost, [1918] Tues morning; ALS, 3 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918] Tues morning; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley and Irma Frost, [1918] Tues noon; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918] Wed afternoon; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918] Wed afternoon; ALS, 2 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918] Thur afternoon; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918] Fri afternoon; ALS, 1 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to [ Lesley Frost] [first page missing], [1918]; ALS, 7 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918]; ALS, 7 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1918-1919]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1919 January 25; ALS, 8 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1919 February 17; ALS, 8 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919 February 25]; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919 February]; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919 February/March]; Envelopes (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1919 March 24; ALS, 5 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919 March]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1919 April 3; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1919 May 20; ALS, 6 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1919 May 22; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919 May 27]; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919] September 19; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1919 November 4; ALS, 5 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919 Fall]; ALS, 6 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919] Sun evening; ALS, 5 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919] Sun evening; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Robert Frost, [1919] Mon afternoon; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919] Tues afternoon; ALS, 7 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919] Wed noon; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919] Fri evening; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost[first page(s) missing], [1919]; ALS, 7 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1919]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, includes poem, "Plowmen," in letter, 1920 January 28; ALS, 6 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, [1920] February 8; ALS, 8 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1920 March 11; ALS, 3 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1920 March 18; ALS, 6 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1920 April 23; ALS, 6 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, [1920] September 23; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, [1920 September]; ALS, 3 p. (Box 7)
      - [ Elinor Frost] to Lesley Frost(incomplete), [1920 September]; AL, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1920 October 14; ALS, 10 p. (Box 7)
      - [Elinor Frost] to Lesley and Irma Frost, [1920 October]; AL, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1920 Fall]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1920] Tues morning; ALS, 6 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1920]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, [1926 April 17]; ALS, 6 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, [1926 April 17]; ALS, 3 p. (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, [1926 April 17]; ALS, 7 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to "Dear Kidds", [1926 April 17]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 7)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [ante 1928? September]; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1928 August 3; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1928 August 21; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 7)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, [1928 September 1]; ALS, 12 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, [1928 September 11]; ALS, 6 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1928 September 18; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1928] October 1; ALS, 4 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1928] Sun morning; ALS, 6 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1928] Mon evening; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1928] Fri morning; ALS, 4 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, [1928]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis[first two pages missing], [1929]; ALS, 3 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, ca. 1930; ALS, 4 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1933]; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1934 April 20; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1934 April]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1934 November 13]; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1934 December 8]; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1934]; ALS, 6 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1934]; ALS, 9 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1935 January 23]; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1935 March 23; ALS, 4 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1935 October 8]; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1935]; ALS, 7 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1937 September 30]; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis[first pages missing], [1937 October 25]; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1938 September 7; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1938 November 30; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1939 February 3]; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1939 February 25; ALS, 8 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1939]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1939]; ALS, 7 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1940]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [ca. 1940]; ALS, 3 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1941 February 12]; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1941 November 17]; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1942 October 8; ALS, 4 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1942; Envelope (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1943 April 24]; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1943 July 9; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1943 October 14; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1943] December 21; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis(incomplete--letter cut), [1943 December]; AL, 3 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1944 September 2; ALS, 3 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1945 April 3; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1950 July 18; ALS, 4 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1950] July 31; ALS, 1 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, [1950]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1951 January 19; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1951 June 20; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Francis, 1951 December 19; ALS, 1 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Ballantine, [1954 May 1]; ALS, 2 p. w/env (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost Ballantine[initialed "R. F." but not by Frost], 1963 January 12; TL, 1 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, Mon afternoon; ALS, 6 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, Wed afternoon; ALS, 6 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, Wed afternoon; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, Wed; ALS, 1 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, Thurs morning; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, Fri noon; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Elinor Frost to Lesley Frost, Fri afternoon; ALS, 2 p. (Box 8)
      - Robert Frost to Raymond Flynt Roberts, 1938 September 10; ALS (copy), 1 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to John S. Van E. Kohn, 1938 September 10; ALS (copy), 1 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to John S. Van E. Kohn, 1950 December 18; ALS (copy), 1 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1918 September 28; ALS, 3 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost[incomplete], [ca. 1918-1919]; ALS, 4 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1919 March 29; ALS, 5 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1919 April 16; ALS, 7 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1919 May 10; ALS, 4 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1920 March 22; Envelope (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1938 November 9; Envelope (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, [1942] March 6; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Lesley Frost, 1948 August 30; ALS, 6 p. w/env (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, 1921 July 23; ALS, 3 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, 1921 September 21; ALS, 3 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, 1922 June 11; ALS, 3 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, 1922 July 28; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, 1923 December 30; ALS, 4 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, 1924 May 24; ALS, 3 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, 1924 August 26; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - Elinor Frost to Mrs. Bromley, n.y. September 6; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - Elinor Frost to Mrs. Bromley, n.y. October 27; ALS, 4 p. (Box 9)
      - Elinor Frost to Mrs. Bromley, n.y. November 10; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - Elinor Frost to Mrs. Bromley, n.y. December 27; ALS, 6 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, n.d.; ALS, 3 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, n.d.; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, n.d.; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, n.d.; ALS, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, n.d.; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, n.d.; ALS, 3 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bromley, n.d.; ALS, 3 p. (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bernice S. Lurie, 1925 February 26; ALS, 5 p. w/env (Box 9)
      - Robert Frost to Mrs. Bernice S. Lurie, 1925 March 25; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 9)
      - Elinor Frost to Mrs. Harry [ Bernice S.] Lurie, [1925] May 11; ALS, 5 p. w/env (Box 9)
      - Elinor Frost to Mrs. Bernice S. Lurie, [1925] September 2; ALS, 4 p. w/env (Box 9)
      - Elinor Frost to Mrs. Bernice S. Lurie, [1925] December 4; ALS, 3 p. w/env (Box 9)
      - Wilfred Wilson Gibson to [Robert Frost], 1913 August 23; ALS, 1 p. (Box 9)
      - Wrappers addressed to Prof. Lawrance Thompson, Princeton, New Jersey, in Robert Frost's hand, Boston, Massachusetts, [1936]; ANS, 2 p. (Box 9)
      - Catharine A[bercrombie]to Lesley Frost, 1914 November 8; APCS, 2 p. (Box 9)
        Writing about her family.
      - George H. Browne to Lesley Frost, n.d.; ANS, 1 p. (Box 9)
        Concerning a dinner engagement.
      - Elizabeth Chandler to Lesley Frost, 1919 February 14; ALS, 3 p. (Box 9)
        Informing her of Charles Chandler's return home, strikes in England, shortages in the country, and life in Ledburyduring the war.
      - Dorothy C[anfield] F[isher]to Lesley Frost, [ca. 1915-18] June 4; APCS (Box 9)
        Agreeing to autograph anything she wants.
      - Delphis Gardner to Lesley Frost, n.d.; ALS, 4 p. (Box 9)
        Writing of his activities at St. Felix School and the return of the school to the east coast of England.
      - Lesley Frost to Delphis Gardner, 1915 December 20; ALS, 2 p. on 1 l. (Box 9)